sup everyone cameras on e5 here with a
very special view today
now you probably know what this video is
about because you have already read the
title
but if if you haven't read the title yet
i'll tell you
this video is called Sonic Underground
why ben hurst is a [ __ ] [ __ ] you see
i was looking at this interview with ben
hurst
to see what I could find about sock
Underground and [ __ ] and
let's just say he doesn't say good
things and that kind of pissed me off
you see right away he starts
by saying I'm sorry if saga was a
disappointment to some of you
no no who who didn't like sock
Underground
[ __ ] the fact that he he had the
audacity to say
like I'm sorry if soccer was a
disappointment
no just no and then he gonna say
but hopefully sega will decide to do
another and maybe this time
i'll have a hand in its development that
would be nice
know that no that would not be nice ben
hurst you have already
you have already showed the [ __ ] in your
ass you have already showed your true
colors
you have only already showed your show
showed how you are you do not lock sock
on the ground
you literally said you think it was a
disappointment
[ __ ] you [ __ ] [ __ ] whoever is in your
family
and and you know what i'll say it it's a
good thing you're dead
that's right [ __ ] ben us he's not
alive anymore
he's [ __ ] dead maybe because I pooped
on him
i don't know you can prove that [ __ ] but
yeah he's dead
so no he's never getting gang sock
Underground
back he doesn't deserve that [ __ ]
now let me move on to wow really made
this video
and you can't see the question but
somebody asked
because they could add songs with the
whole
soxomatic thing and collect as originals
from a s c a p b m
i good that's what they should be doing
[ __ ] do you not know do you not know
how tv shows work
if if somebody comes to you and say
we need you to make socks on around you
just say
yes if somebody asks me to make soccer
Underground
i'll be like [ __ ] ah I already i
already have it done
go look at my youtube channel I don't
give a [ __ ] about you [ __ ] you do not
know what the [ __ ] you talk about
ben huss or should I call you poopyhurst
because that's all you have to me okay
then he says here's her sock and what
happened
after setting was canned which is a good
thing i'll add
because of a change in leadership at abc
good
i don't know who the [ __ ] abc is but
they probably [ __ ] suck and
low reigns caused by multiple
preemptions caused by
sporting events and finally being placed
up against
the red up power rangers barriers are
cool we love them
now there's some cheese programming
strategy yeah like sock on the ground
this is a new version of Sonic was
created
the song coming up that's right
something good
to stand up against the [ __ ]
parents if you're going to be standing
up against tommy
you cannot use saddam if you're going up
against the legendary tommy
from like the parents you need mac the
Hedgehog green versus green
you pick up one burn down [ __ ] then
he says
did they ask me me what kind name is pat
that's [ __ ] stupid
no nobody's gonna ask pat anything len
is pretty cool nobody's gonna give up
pat
who you didn't even put his last name n
we don't even know who they are
al thanks to you [ __ ] do you have do
you develop a series
no in fact I never heard of the series
before a dick story editor called and
asked me and pat
who the [ __ ] is pat who the [ __ ]
do I do I go I i know everyone who works
on
i do not know pat who the [ __ ] is pap
[ __ ] is he called pack could he pat
your ass [ __ ]
it like do you hate talking that much
that you need to
oh pass bang my fat ass like tell me how
much soccer around
sucks that's my [ __ ] turn on oh i
love you pat
[ __ ] pat and [ __ ] youtube and us I'm
glad you're dead
then you're going to say forsak on the
ground I refuse why would you refuse
ben hurst asking you they're asking you
do you want a job to make sakura
that's not even a job is it truly a job
if you're doing what you love
a job would be taking a poopy and not
getting paid
I'm sorry [ __ ] like sagan that's not a
job
that's fun
i refused we don't I don't know what
that means we don't do car calls which
for those of you are familiar with them
i just I don't know what it means is
where they bring in about 20 hours to
learn about series
and picture it in premises for free good
good good [ __ ] if somebody came in and
said
we're going to make a show about buying
a month club Dresden
i don't got i'll come in for free i'll
pay you to come in
you picking up one boy now [ __ ] in
hopes of snagging
an episode too the story editor got us
there by guaranteeing us
at least a few episodes so off we went
for the conference room at
dick okay we got the and yup
20 riders good that's how much you need
to write a show
they showed up in episode of Saturday
and why it sucks to illustrate the
backgrounds of the characters
well that's it they didn't care about
socks at him
because it [ __ ] sucks like I’ve been
saying it wasn't one of mine
or pat's who the [ __ ] is it was one of
the other episodes
i described the marvelous new direction
siblings music
missing mother stupid new stupid new
characters
oh oh no [ __ ]
[ __ ] we got a poopy baby [ __ ] in the
house
we got a [ __ ] we got a [ __ ] we got a
[ __ ] who pooped
his pants he doesn't know what he's
talking about
take your [ __ ] [ __ ] away pat we do
not want that anymore
they says they ended the meeting okay we
were taken to another room with the
story editor and they told us
they want us to write the pops up good i
would that would be fun
they said we did sega with the script
then the syrian was fired
and we were hired they also hired
another team of studios who survived
through about af
before they left so so good it showed
that Sonic
Underground had a lot of people's
visions while working the show
that's a good thing [ __ ] like I'm just
saying
we also got a few fledgling rides shoved
down our throats by the producers reason
i had to go rewrite
the damn use of grips from page one they
still got paid for the script I got nada
good you suck no one likes you ben huss
so that's the saga of su as I rewatch
some episodes
I'm surprised it's as good as it is i
that's what I’ve been saying you [ __ ]
[ __ ]
are you kidding me oh you are pooping on
my butt are you [ __ ] kidding me
like it took you it took you like what
six all paragraphs
to end up by saying it's good
I'm fully aware it doesn't match up it
don't need to match up
it's like it's the [ __ ] tits like uh
uh
it don't have to match up to [ __ ]
selling [ __ ]
sucks ben huss I'm glad you're dead
i
okay and he stops talking about soccer
[ __ ] that [ __ ]
that's the end [ __ ] ben hurst bye